yourtango.com 2018-12-26

# Tango Publishing Corp Privacy Policy – Updated 2018 | YourTango

Tango Publishing Corporation, a New York Corporation (“Company,” “we,” or “us”), knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by the Company when you use our Website and related services (the “Service”), how the information will be used and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Information We Collect**

 **Information You May Choose to Provide to Us**

We may collect information, including personally identifiable information, directly from you if you choose to provide that information. For example, you may provide us with your name and contact information (such as an email address), date of birth, or other details of that nature, when you sign up for our newsletters or participate in promotions or surveys on the Site. For the newsletter subscriptions we use Mailchimp as the provider, you can check out their [privacy policy here](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

You also may choose to provide personally identifiable information about yourself when you participate in discussions on the Site. Please be aware that information you post in these discussions/comments may be viewed or captured by anyone who visits the Site, therefore you should avoid posting sensitive personal information that you would not want to be available to the public.

You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and email address, when you register with the Service. Also, you may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, poll and surveys, message boards and comments, email messages and newsletters and other interactive areas of our Website (all such information and material, “User Content”). When you register we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, zip code and other information on you and your personal interests. Once you register with YourTango and log on to our services, you are not anonymous to us. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

 **Cookies Information**

A cookie does not collect any personal information about you from which your individual identity can be established. This website uses cookies and other tracking tools, placed either by us or our third-party partners and providers. When you visit the Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, for example, your IP address (your computer’s location on the Internet) and our cookie information (if installed). We may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies the type of browser you are using and allows Company to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Website. We use information that is collected for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see (such as banner advertising), facilitate product and content development, improve our services, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. Company uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can set your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Therefore, some features of the Service may not function properly or at all if the ability to accept all cookies is disabled. Other cookies and tracking tools collect information about your browsing habits in order to help us and advertisers make suggestions relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited, and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers, to provide you with more personalized advertisements when visiting other websites. This might happen on our own websites or on websites run by separate companies. These tracking tools will collect information on what parts of our websites interest you - in other words, your behavior or browsing history. We also work with outside partners who help us gather this information. These partners help us both on our websites as well as outside websites. You can opt-out of having us collect and share this information by following our opt-out methods below. Please note that the choices you make are browser-specific. So, if you use a different browser, you will need to opt out again. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer or mobile device without your explicit consent. Your browser “help” section will normally provide details on how to manage the cookie settings.

 **Device and Connection Information** :

We collect information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other devices you use to access the Services. This device information includes your connection type and settings when you install, access, update, or use our Services. We also collect information through your device about your operating system, browser type, IP address, URLs of referring/exit pages, device identifiers, and crash data. We use your IP address and/or country preference in order to approximate your location to provide you with a better Service experience.  How much of this information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Services.  Server and data center Service administrators can disable collection of this information via the administrator settings or prevent this information from being shared with us by blocking transmission at the local network level.  

 **Log File Information**

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our Website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and other such information.

 **Clear Gifs Information**

When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your Company account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing and make us better for our users.

 _New Technology_

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means and there may be other technologies present which act in a similar way but are protected by confidentiality.

 **How We Use Your Information**

  1. We may use the information gathered on YourTango for various purposes, including the purposes listed below. For example, if you were to contact us with a question and provide your email address, we would use the email address you provided to respond to your inquiry. In addition, we use information we collect from you and through the Site to:
  2. Provide products and services you request (such as when you sign up to receive our email newsletters); Respond to requests, questions, and comments, and provide other types of user support; 
  3. Offer you services, or direct you to portions of this Site or other websites, that we believe may interest you; 
  4. Carry out, evaluate, and improve our business (which may include developing new features for the Site; analyzing and enhancing the user experience on the Site; assessing the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising; and managing our communications); 
  5. Perform data analytics regarding usage of the Site (including market and customer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal information); 
  6. Guard against, identify, and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims, and other liabilities; and 
  7. Comply with applicable legal requirements, law enforcement requests, and our company policies.
  8. We use the information you submit (including any personal information) to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, to customize the advertising and content you see (such as banner advertising), facilitate product and content development, improve our services, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. By using the Service, you consent to this use and any other use of information identified in this Privacy Policy.

Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service (for instance, in User Content you post on message boards or in comments) becomes available to the public. You should be aware that even if you remove User Content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content.

 **Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

 **General**

To edit your account, you only need to log into your account and make the necessary changes on the toolbar items provided once you have successfully logged into your account. To delete the YourTango Account and information, log into your personal account and under the edit account tab at the bottom of the page find the Cancel Account option. Once you have requested your account be cancelled from the YourTango site you will be emailed a confirmation request after selecting the link your account will be deleted along with your information. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our website, such as service announcements, administrative messages and our e-mail newsletters if you have opted-in for them. You, of course, have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. Please be advised that we may archive information we collect on our members and visitors.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our website, such as service announcements, administrative messages and our e-mail newsletters if you have opted-in for them. You, of course, have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. Please be advised that we may archive information we collect on our members and visitors.

 **Opt-In/Opt-Out**

Upon registration or from time-to-time, you may be asked to indicate whether you are interested in receiving information from us about special offers or news about our products, services, and advertisers. You may also be provided with the opportunity to opt-in to receive offers directly from select companies other than us. If you do choose to receive these communications by means of an opt-in, we will occasionally send you an e-mail message that matches your request(s). You may, of course, always choose not to receive any of this information from us. We currently provide the following opt-out opportunities:

  1. Upon registration, you can choose to receive no communications from us other than an initial member welcome message.
  2. At any time, you can follow a link provided in every newsletter or e-mail message to unsubscribe from that mailing list or e-mail service.
  3. Please note that we reserve the right to contact you in the event of a change in our Terms of Service or this privacy policy.

Company may use certain information about you and/or your User Content without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security and personalizing advertisements and promotions.

Company reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the User Content you post on the Website. Company has the right to remove any such User Content for any reason or no reason, including, without limitation, if in its sole opinion, such User Content violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Use or to protect or defend Company’s rights or property or those of any third-party. Company also reserves the right to remove User Content upon the request of any third-party.

We use cookies, clear gifs and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of the Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in to the Website.

 **How We Share Your Information**

 **Personally, Identifiable Information**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Company will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others.

Company may share your personally identifiable information with our affiliates and third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Company (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers or dissolution.

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Company will not disclose personal information to any third-party unless required to do so by law, regulation or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates or investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies or to protect the security or integrity of our Website; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property or personal safety of Company, our users or others. Please note we may not provide notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

 **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with third parties to help them and us understand the usage patterns for certain Company services.

Company allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

Company does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Company to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. The Company privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such advertisers.

 **How We Protect Your Information**

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful, or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure, or use. That said, it is not possible to guarantee the security of information transmitted online, and you assume some risk with regard to the security of information you provide through any website, including this Site. If you have a data security inquiry, you may contact us by emailing [security@yourtango.com](mailto:security@yourtango.com).

Company uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Company makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Company, at all times.

 **Compromise of Personal Information**

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Company will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by applicable law.

Your Choices About Your Personal Information

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information to Company, in which case Company may not be able to provide certain services to you.

 **Children's Privacy**

We care about the safety of children and take the protection of children’s privacy very seriously. Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to Company. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [webmaster@yourtango.com](mailto:webmaster@yourtango.com).

 **Third Parties**

Company expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our Website, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information (including personally identifiable information) on blogs, message boards, comments or other sharing areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and outside the scope of this document.

Company is not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Website nor the information or content contained therein. It follows that the Company accepts no responsibility for events experienced by you if you visit a third-party site by clicking through from the Website. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Website to another website, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. User browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our Website, is subject to that other website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

 **Third Party Advertisements and Technologies:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Website as is explained in detail in the Website's Terms of Use. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or other advertising technology may be placed on your browser. This advertising technology uses information derived from your visits to the Website to target advertising within this Website. This information is used for many purposes; for example, it helps us try to ensure that you do not see the same advertisements over and over again. We also use this information to help select and display targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you (sometimes called “online behavioral advertising” or “interest-based advertising” or “OBA”). We also use web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this Website, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Website and to deliver more relevant advertising.

In addition, our advertisers or other third parties may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on the Website and other websites. We do not control the data collection and use practices of these other third parties. You should read the privacy notices of the websites you visit in order to determine what companies may be collecting information on those websites.

 **Your Choices**

 **Unsubscribe from emails**.

To unsubscribe from a particular newsletter, click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of that email newsletter.

Blocking cookies. Certain browsers may be configured to notify you when you receive cookies or allow you to restrict or disable certain cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, however, that could affect certain features of the Site that use cookies to enhance their functionality. NAI (Network Advertising Initiative).

If you choose to not see the same advertisement, please see [link for the ability to opt-out via the Network Advertising Initiative. ](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/)

**Payment Information:**  

We collect certain payment and billing information when you register for certain paid Services.  For example, we ask you to designate a billing representative, including name and contact information, upon registration.  You might also provide payment information, such as payment card details, which we collect via secure payment processing services.

 **Notification Procedures**

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business-related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Website, as determined by Company in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute acceptance of those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and law that applied at the time the information was collected.

 **How to Contact the Company**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Website or your dealings with the Website (including your choices regarding cookies), please contact us by email at [webmaster@yourtango.com](mailto:webmaster@yourtango.com), or send mail to:

Attn: General Manager

 **Tango Publishing Corporation**

 **101 West 79th Street, Suite 2G**

 **New York, NY 10024**

* * *
